Jhal
a very good morning friends welcome you to
8 questions drive safe mission possible and have
started with a new set of questions
asked in question of the siddhanta day which gather answers the question
of death Anil Singh
Verma Kasana welcome you to the and Russian team
mission to make roads safer ko hai is the
question and this screen editing see you are
driving anti kilometer par r the
alarms pet is ched kilometer par r you
notice the camera and you will not just for the
camera and increase pay and smile for camera
to make a nice pic shabri for you hua tha
money to pay fine and de release camera
is to anu sachiv driving behaviour and
arrive at speed limit even after crossing
the camera question appointed subscription on
daily basis which are coming back for travelling is something
driving kilometers in the
mid kilometer then what we do the time please
answer this question and  Be a part of our
mission and less joint gathering everyday see the
question answers-08 The alarm
goes off at the kilometer. If you are
driving at 80 kilometer
speed, when you are
coming to the confirmed kilometer of the place where the speed limit is,
you also noticed that there is a speed
camera ahead, then what will you do at that time,
just for the camera, you will increase your
speed and just because of the camera, you will
reduce your speed for the time being and then
increase your speed, smile for the camera to make a
nice picture, and what is happening, you will
give a good picture word or else you will
drive fast, sensitive, half means quiet, be
defined and keep driving, name doon
bodhak, how much is the fine because you have a lot of
money to pay the fine, release the
camera is to end the rest save drive, keep driving, keep
driving under the HP limit, even after
crossing the camera,
you will reduce your speed, you will come to the
speed limit and then
you will remain within the speed limit, even if you
cross that camera,  Wrinkles
with us and give your answer and get a chance to
buy many exciting gifts. The
man requests you to join the
English word of Kundli at your loved ones can also
join the only friends and family members also have chance to win
prizes for
men and Supriya Pathak the other liquid
fuel in this love subscribe school college
to these NGOs and driving behavior
on the road will now I request you to kindly
follow and doctors behavior honesty truth will make
everyday this is a very thing
in metropolitan cities there are cameras installed that
check speed a lot of
people do that they come very fast and do
something in front of the camera, there is a
speed limit,
keep subscribing till then that they have
mastered what is this, the tightening that you have to do is that
how well you are able to maintain that thing
and if you have been told to
drive an equal kilometer ahead or behind then they request
you to stick to the speed limit
All the safety measures related to Chalen Aao are
for our safety and
not for anyone else. The day we will modify this thing
in our behavior when we will
understand that these are rules and regulations,
they are only for us, then we will be
successful in making our day successful.
You can see that there is a question on the screen.
You have 2 answers
of Rs. One of the questions is a question with you. You have
subscribed and participated in the
World of Work.
Announcement of the results of annual
return of the result S8 Showlanki speaking
at 10 pm. You can be a part of the development
and you can see years as well. You can go
to your website to check your result. So here is
the question on-screen. Driving speed at
6 km per Arvind alarms. At 6 km are you going to notice speed camera
head you will not just for the camera and
increase page body my father camera to make
a nice picture.  Kanchana drive passed since you have
money to pay fine, release camera to
students, driving behavior and
drive speed limit even after crossing
camera, please join us, give your answers
and we can earn a lot of
sliding price, so well, whatever your
knowledge, whatever your skills, whatever
fears related to everyday and appropriate related to it, they are
also in these, so we would
request you to make your love partner,
your friends in Shamli border
also a part of this entire campaign and you
can win many exciting
prizes and keeping those people safe, keeping
yourself safe is also your responsibility
and somewhere you can become a
part of this entire cabinet with us by joining this mission and
our death rates are
so many accidents happen everyday,
help us in working on them, now you
can see the question on the screen
for you, will you have you are driving at 60
km, Arvind alarms the victim is
going at 60 km, while the speed is that  It
is sixty kilometers
in Odisha speed camera and you notice
that there is a speed camera ahead now what will you do, at
that time you will reduce your speed
because there is a speed camera ahead and then you will
increase your speed, smile at the
camera to make a nice picture, you will smile and
look towards that camera so that a
nice picture is captured, you have generated drive
passed since you have money to pay fine, you will keep typing
fast and because you have a
lot of money to finally remove the
cameras to install, you will control your driving
behavior and drive speed limit even after
crossing camera, we will come to the speed limit of our state's
cameras on the roads
and then further also, that means now
even after the camera is removed, you will continue to
maintain the same speed, so please take your
answers
and this will be a great chance to win some very exciting
prizes, it will be a part
of those and make and everyday for those
who have changed their wives everyday but
when you understand all the rules and
regulations  It is for our safety,
for the safety of our loved ones, the
road accidents will
reduce to a great extent that day, but the thing is that it will
come to almost zero, but you will have to
change your behavior a little bit every day, as
much as the link means opposition, there are
many things in India, like in boxing,
if you drive a car, then for the changes that happen in the back seat,
point Mintu
Vestige bell button, I request you that please
if you are sitting in the back seat, then wear seat belt,
this is your safety, if any
miss happens, then because of the seat belt, it is
always yours, that is
why you can make up for it, now in that accident,
its importance will
reduce to some extent, so
you mix and that when you are sitting in the back seat, that is, even in the back, then
you should sit with belts and if
we compare means that if
I talk about small children, then there is a huge problem with computer games, then
drive a car because
we forbid distraction driving,
you should not want distraction driving,
you should avoid it.  To make any small
child sit on the Ambani thing in front of you
because the
distraction that Hussain gets into is
because he is sporting a moustache, if he does something then the
chances of action increase a lot.
You should avoid screens these days and
not because of the inbuilt features but because of the external
screens in which you can play video songs,
you should avoid them
because they cause distractions and the
chances of distraction increase a lot. Do
not use your mobile phone while driving as the
alarms become very risky
not only for you but also for those who are
with you and anyone else who is
walking on the side.
One carelessness of yours
can take someone else's life, so
we should not do that kind of behavior,
if you change small things then
we will be successful in making our day successful. If we
talk about two-
wheelers, if people have to
go for a short distance then they do
not wear helmets but they do wear helmets.  It
is very important to apply it because the hair match
creates a layer of it on your hair, a covering which protects your health from
any accident.
So whenever you drive please
buy only ISI marked helmet and always wear it if
you are a passenger and always wear the
helmet of the right size. Never
buy one that is loose or tight. If it is loose then the helmet will get pulled out due to an
accident. If it is loose then the
helmet will get pulled out
and if it is tight then it will
create problems for you somewhere or the other. It will cause discomfort for you and will also cause destruction while
driving. It is very important for us to have the necessary
science while driving.
So always be focused and
always be focused. If we
want to drive well then if we take care of these small
things then we
can make our rotis set and only responsibility is on them while
driving.
We are definitely using the road and taking care of all
those things.  There is an
increase in the number of people using YouTube to save their lives,
whether it is our phone
or heavy vehicle or
train ride, there is also the responsibility of maintaining distance, to
make your rotis only, do
not cross the crowded road, if you have to cross, then
always cross only and only,
use the foot overbridge here,
use the underpass here, do
not use the source and if you have to do it out of
compulsion, then always
drive after looking whether someone is
coming from behind, stop for a while and if you are
going to turn suddenly, then do
not stand in the middle of the road
because it can create confusion for others as well
and the chances of accident
can increase, if we all
fulfill our responsibilities well,
then we will be successful in making our rotis, this is
our
entire mission, just drive mission possible,
we will be able to complete it and this death tax
which is on the top  jaata ja raha hai humare
road accident tele iss par jo itne saare
log jaate hain usko kahi na kahin hum why aur kar
apne rolle ko set par na
paayenge so editing see all my screen
question is visible you have enrolled into its
time to answer this question after the
no renewal comment with any specific question sahej the
question you are driving
reddy kilometers par arvind alarms pet
6 kilometers par are you notice speed camera and
head couple slow ravan just for the camera and
sanskars pay smile for the camera to make a
nice pic sabri drafts you have money to pay
fine releaser camera into english so aisi
survavir
milk drive meaning speed love match even after
crossing camera please join us
register your answers aur mein
oil ka time oil usne to varna dashanand stay
tuned thank you so much shesh stay
healthy thank you for debate on